-put together catalog for light curve identification
   -might lead to a paper, either individual or part of larger paper
   -merge catalog with other catalogs (catalina survey)
   -catalina survey overlaps heavily with sdss stripe82 
   -use astropy to match catalogs via coordinates
   -christina continues work on catalog (80% is unfinished)
   -try to create algorithms to label sources
   -fats? (drawbacks: only 1 band)
   -sampling issues (some periods look like 1 day)
   -work of having a reliable catalog first 
-outlier detection
   -what are the features of weird objects, why are they strange?
-outlier v new class
   -an object whose average distance between other objects, is very big (so probably not part of the milky way)
   -outliers have highest weirdness scores
   -matrix feature shared to identify outliers
-redshift correction for quasars?

